

SOFTWARE ENGINEER · DEEP LEARNING PRACTITIONER

Pune. India

□+91-9730115914 | ■syncerax@gmail.com | ★syncerax.com | □syncerax | □syncerax |

Profile

I am a software engineer who loves to make things. I'm experienced in Android development and I enjoy Deep Learning and Web development. I love puzzles and challenges. Apart from Computer Science, I enjoy reading, photography, badminton, trekking and playing the piano.

Skills

Programming Languages

PYTHON, JAVA, C, C++, JAVASCRIPT

· Proficient in Data Structures and Algorithms, Object Oriented Programming, Scripting

Android Development

ADEPT AT MODERN ANDROID DEVELOPMENT USING ARCHITECTURE COMPONENTS

- Basics: Activities, Fragments, Lifecycles, Intents
- Architecture Components: ViewModel, LiveData, Data Binding, Room Persistence Library
- UI: ConstraintLayout, RecyclerView, Styles, Drawables
- Libraries: Volley, Dagger

Deep Learning

COMFORTABLE WITH BUILDING AND TRAINING NEURAL NETWORKS USING PYTHON

- Machine Learning and Neural Networks: Regression, Classification models, Feedforward Neural Networks
- Computer Vision: Convolutional Neural Networks, Pretrained networks, Transfer learning, Fine-tuning, Object detection
- Natural Language Processing: Recurrent Neural Networks, LSTMs, Sentiment Analysis, Language models
- Libraries: TensorFlow, Keras, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Matplotlib

Web Development

FAMILIAR WITH WEB DEVELOPMENT AND DATABASE MANAGEMENT SYSTEMS

• Server side: Python (Django, Flask); Frontend: HTML5, CSS, JavaScript; Databases: MySQL, SQLite, MongoDB

Others - Version Control, Cloud Platforms, Typesetting, Design

GIT / GOOGLE CLOUD PLATFORM, JEKYLL + GITHUB PAGES, GOOGLE APPS SCRIPT / LATEX, MARKDOWN / ADOBE XD

Experience

Raja Software Labs Pvt. Ltd.

Pune, India

June 2019 - Present

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

TWALE ENGINEER

- Implementing new features and fixing bugs
- Adding enhancements to existing features
- · Designing and conducting training sessions for resource induction
- Automating the annual appraisal process at RSL

ArrayPointer Pune, India

MACHINE LEARNING INTERN

May 2018 - Oct. 2018

- · Developed a recommendation system for sending personalised push notifications on an Android newspaper application
- Deployed as a JSON API using Flask

Education

Bachelor of Engineering in Information Technology (GPA: 8.83)

Pune, India

SAVITRIBAI PHULE PUNE UNIVERSITY (a.k.a. UNIVERSITY OF PUNE)

Sep. 2015 - June 2019

Certifications

Deep Learning - 5 Course Specialization

Coursera - deeplearning.ai

Nov. 2018

- · Neural Networks and Deep Learning
- Improving Deep Neural Networks: Hyper-parameter tuning, Regularization and Optimization
- Structuring Machine Learning Projects
- Convolutional Neural Networks
- Sequence Models